<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Juliana Faccio Lima</title>
    <link>https://julianaflima.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Juliana Faccio Lima</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 10:03:59 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://julianaflima.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Courses | Juliana Lima</title>
      <link>https://julianaflima.github.io/current/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 10:03:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianaflima.github.io/current/</guid>
      <description>Syllabi and reading schedules coming soon!

 PHI 1000 - Introduction to Philosophy  This is an Introduction to Philosophy course. We will read and discuss theories about traditional topics in philosophy about the nature of mind, the nature of knowledge, personal identity, and free will. But we will also discuss more recent topics, such as:  social ontology: how, why, and if concepts of race, gender, and disability are social constructs; social epistemology: how knowledge and desires we have come from others, and how to avoid falling into epistemic &amp;ldquo;traps&amp;rdquo;, such as echo chambers and epistemic bubbles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Past Courses | Juliana Lima</title>
      <link>https://julianaflima.github.io/past_courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 09:18:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianaflima.github.io/past_courses/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the syllabus of courses I have taught:
 Critical Thinking Seminar: Philosophy of Mind Introduction to Philosophy of Language Critical Thinking  I actively seek feedback from my students with mid-semester evaluations. Here you&amp;rsquo;ll find three different mid-semester evaluations I typically give to students: a general course evaluation, a course evaluation students take right after they submit their midterm assignment without knowing their grades, and another after they get back their graded midterm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syllabi | Juliana Lima</title>
      <link>https://julianaflima.github.io/sample_syllabi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julianaflima.github.io/sample_syllabi/</guid>
      <description>Over my academic career, I had the opportunity to observe many different courses. Here&amp;rsquo;s some sample syllabi of courses I&amp;rsquo;d like to teach.
Note: I update my syllabi regularly. Always check this page to make sure you have the latest version!
 Intro to Philosophy Intro to Ethics Ethics of Robots Thoughts from the First-Person Perspective -- Philosophy of Mind (Introduction) Mind and Action: from the Individual to the Collective Philosophy of Language (Advanced) Modern Logic  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>